A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.5 FA1843
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Policy - General, 900; 89.85 Cubic Feet 233 containers
  - Program and Policy - General (No program letter)
    - Program and Policy - Communication for Social Change - Supplementary Material, c. 2001 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth (5) Week 1, c. 2008 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth (5) Week 2, c. 2008 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth (5) Week 3, c. 2008 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth (5) Week 4, c. 2008 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth, 2007-2008 (Box 76, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth, 2008-2013 (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth, 2008-2013 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture (Theme), 1999-2002 (Box 77, Folder 4-5, Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture (Theme), 2003-2007 (Box 78, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture (Theme), 2003-2007 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      Resticted - Personnel - Open in 2078
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture (Theme) - Supplementary Material, 1996-2000 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Culture and Development Project, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2067
    - Program and Policy - Declinations, 1915-2000 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Declinations - Manuals, 1974-1983 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Minutes, 1963-1985 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Minutes, 1963-1985 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2056
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Minutes, 1986-1991 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2062
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2066
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Minutes, 1996-1999 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2070
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 4, Box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 3-4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1983-1987 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4, Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 4, Box 86, Folder 1-6)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 4, Box 88, Folder 1-4, Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity, 1998-2005 (Box 90, Folder 4, Box 91, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Supplementary Material, 1980s-1990s (Box 91, Folder 5, Box 92, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Reports, 1970s (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Reports, 1980s (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Reports, 1990s (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Supplementary Material (Box 93, Folder 4, Box 94, Folder 1-4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Reports - Briefing Book on the Urban Poor Program, c. 1986 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Supplementary Material (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Supplementary Material (Box 96, Folder 1-4, Box 97, Box 98, Folder 1-3, Box 99)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Supplementary Material (Box 100, Folder 1-2, Box 101, Folder 1-3, Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - History, 1978-1980; 1983-1986 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - History, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2048
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - History - Supplementary Material, c. 1985 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Review, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Review, 1983-1985 (Box 104, Folder 2-3, Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity - Review - Supplementary Material, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity Subcommittee, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity Subcommittee - Supplementary Material, c. 1967 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1980-2002 (Box 106, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1993-2002 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1998-2001 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 2002-2004 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1997-2011 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1997-2011 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Evaluation - Supplementary Material (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy, 1996-1999 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Equity in Food Systems, 2011-2012 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Food Markets, 2013 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security, 1999-2003 (Box 109, Folder 3-4, Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security, 2004-2012 (Box 110, Folder 2-3, Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security, 2013 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security, 2013 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security - Trip Reports, 1971-2011 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security - Trip Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security - Supplementary Material (Box 112, Folder 1-2, Box 113, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Fund for New York City, 1993-2006 (Box 113, Folder 4, Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Gender and Women's Leadership, 2011-2014 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Gender and Women's Leadership, 2011-2014 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Geographix Focus, 1998-2004 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program - Minutes, 1989-2000 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program, 1998-2001 (Box 115, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program, 1989-1991 (Box 115, Folder 4, Box 116, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program, 1992-1993 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program, 1994-1997 (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program - Supplementary Material (RIO +5) (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program - Larocco Associates, 1989-1992 (Box 118, Folder 2-3, Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Global Inclusion (Cross Theme), 2003 (Box 119, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Inclusion (Cross Theme), 2003 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Global Inclusion (Cross Theme), 1999-2002 (Box 119, Folder 4, Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Global Inclusion - Population and Cairo Agenda, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Global Equity and Engagement, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Global Impact Investing Network, 2009-2011 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Knowledge Management, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Global Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Global Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Global Partnership for Resilience, 2013-2016 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Global Partnership for Resilience, 2013-2016 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2087
    - Program and Policy - Grant Processing Regional Offices, 2002-2005 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Grants-In-Aid, 1973-1985 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Grant Reporting and Announcement Procedures, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Growth and Opportunity Fund, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Grant Processing, 1995-2006 (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Grant Processing, 1995-2006 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2027
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity (Theme), 1999-2004 (Box 123, Folder 3, Box 124, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity (Theme), 2005-2009 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity (Theme), 2005-2009 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity (Theme) - Supplementary Material, 1999-2008 (Box 126, Folder 1-4, Box 124, Folder 3, Box 125, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity - Director - Executive Search, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2046
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity - Trip Reports, 2001-2005 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity - Trip Reports - George Brown, 2004-2005 (Box 127, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Equity - Trip Reports - Derek Yach, 2006-2007 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Human and Institutional Capacity Building, 2001-2004 (Box 128, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Influence Fund, 2012-2014 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Informal City Dialogues, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Impact Enterprises for Bop, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Information Policy, 1995-2001 (Box 129, Folder 4-5)
    - Program and Policy - Information Policy, 1995-2001 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2072
    - Program and Policy - Information Policy - Supplementary Material (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Initiatives, 2006-2009 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - Initiatives, 2009-2013 (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Initiatives, 2015 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2086
    - Program and Policy - Initiative Management Team - Minutes, 2007-2014 (Box 131, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Initiative, 2006-2010 (Box 131, Folder 4, Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Initiative, 2011-2014 (Box 132, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Initiative, 2011-2014 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Initiative - Supplementary Material (Box 132, Folder 4, Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Innovations for a Metro Nation, 2009 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Working Group, 2009 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Innovation Working Group, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Innovative Finance, 2012-2014 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Innovative Finance, 2012-2014 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Innovative Projects Fund, 2010-2013 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Innovative Secondary Education for Skill Enhancement, 2011-2012 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - Insecure Property Rights of Women, 2013 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy - Multiple Use Water Services for the Poor, 2010-2012 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Program and Policy - Institutional Overhead, 1939-1994 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - National Smart Power Grid, 2009 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - National Smart Power Grid, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Intellectual Property Rights, 1999-2010 (Box 134, Folder 3-4)
    - Program and Policy - Internal Innovation Fund, 2011 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Internal Work Processes, 2006 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - International Philanthropy, 1989-2009 (Box 136, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - International Philanthropy, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2065
    - Program and Policy - International Security, 1989-1998 (Box 136, Folder 5, Box 137, Folder 1-4, Box 138, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - International Security - North Korea, 1993-1998 (Box 138, Folder 3, Box 139, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Knowledge Management - Digitization of Annual Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 140, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Knowledge Management - Digitization of Annual Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Learning and Liaison Unit, 1999-2001 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Issues Fund, 2012-2013 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Lost Peri-Urban Ecosystems, 2013 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Migration, 2005-2007 (Box 140, Folder 5, Box 141, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Migration, 2005-2007 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2078
    - Program and Policy - New Orleans, 2006-2007 (Box 141, Folder 3-4, Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - New Orleans, 2007-2013 (Box 142, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - New Orleans, 2007-2013 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy - Planning for an Urban Future, 2008 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - New York City Cultural Innovation Fund, 2007-2013 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - New York City Cultural Innovation Fund, 2007-2013 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Program and Policy - New York State 2100 Commission, 2013 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - New York City (NYC) Opportunities Fund, 2006-2013 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - New York City (NYC) Opportunities Fund, 2006-2013 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - North American Transnational Communities (NATC), 2003-2006 (Box 143, Folder 4, Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Oceans, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Oceans, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Office of Strategy and Learning, 2006 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - 100 Resilient Cities Centennial Challenge, 2013-2014 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Opportunities Relaunch Fund - Africa-Asia, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Opportunities Relaunch Fund, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Organizational Excellence, 2011 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Pandemics, 2006-2013 (Box 146, Folder 4-5)
    - Program and Policy - Pandemics, 2006-2013 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Patents Policy, 1964-2001 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - Philanthropic Sector, 2011-2013 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy - Philanthropic Workshop (TPW), 1994-2003 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Philanthropic Workshop (TPW), 1994-2003 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Playbook for Resilient and Inclusive Cities, 2011 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Plant Resistance and Protection, 1964-1986 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Cairo Agenda, 1999-2001 (Box 147, Folder 4-5, Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Cairo Agenda, 1999-2001 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Front of File, 1986-1996 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Front of File (Box 145, Folder 7-8)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Front of File, 1979-1987 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2058
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health, 1988-1989 (Box 148, Folder 3-4)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health, 1990-1993 (Box 150, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health, 1994-1995 (Box 150, Folder 4, Box 151, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health, 1996-2007 (Box 151, Folder 3-4, Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Supplementary Material (Box 152, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Clinical Epidemiology, 1977-1982 (Box 153, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Clinical Epidemiology, 1977-1982 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2053
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Clinical Epidemiology - Supplementary Material (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Director Search, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2029
    - Program and Policy - Prizes, 1992-2012 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Leadership Opportunity Fund, 2012 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Recovery Fund, 2009 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities, 2000 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Potential Searches, 2007-2013 (Box 154, Folder 6-7)
    - Program and Policy - Potential Searches, 2007-2013 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa, 1998-2013 (Box 155, Folder 1-4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa, 1998-2013 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa - Supplementary Material (Box 155, Folder 5, Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Southeast Asia, 2000-2009 (Box 156, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Southeast Asia, 2010-2011 (Box 156, Folder 5, Box 157, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Southeast Asia - Supplementary Material (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices, 1992-2003 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Africa, 1998-2000 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Kenya, 1991-2006 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Kenya, 2005-2013 (Box 159, Folder 1, Box 160)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Mexico, 1945-2003 (Box 161, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - San Francisco, 1999-2006 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Survey, 2006 (Box 161, Folder 4, Box 162, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Thailand, 2000-2013 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Offices - Zimbabwe, 1999 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Results-Based Management Framework (RBM), 2009-2010 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Relief, 2005-2013 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Rio+20 Conference, 2012 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Rockefeller Global Urban Summit (Bellagio), 2007 (Box 163, Folder 5, Box 164, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - RF Socialcast Network, 2010 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform - Minutes, 1991-1998 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform, 1988-1989 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform, 1990-1992 (Box 165, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform, 1992-1997 (Box 165, Folder 4-5, Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform, 1998-2001 (Box 166, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform - Supplementary Material (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Science-Based Development, 1987-1998 (Box 166, Folder 5, Box 167, Folder 1-4, Box 168, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Science and Technology Group, 1983-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Science and Technology Group - Supplementary Material (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Search Partnerships, 2011 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Searchlight Function, 2008-2012 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Searches - US Domestic Secure Livelihoods, 2012-2015 (Box 170, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Searches - US Domestic Secure Livelihoods, 2012-2015 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Senior Management Team, 1999-2006 (Box 171, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Shared Programming, 2002-2006 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Smart Power for Environmentally-Sound Economic Development (SPEED), 2009-2017 (Box 172, Folder 1-2)
      Restricted - Open in 2028
    - Program and Policy - Smart Power for Environmentally-Sound Economic Development (SPEED), 2009-2017 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2088
    - Program and Policy - Social Investing, 2012-2017 (Box 172, Folder 3-5)
    - Program and Policy - Social Investing, 2012-2017 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - South Africa, 1985-1991 (Box 174, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - South Africa, 1991-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE), 1973-1994 (Box 175, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE), 1982-1998 (Box 175, Folder 4, Box 176, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Special International Initiatives, 1991-1998 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Special International Initiatives, 1991-1998 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programming - Front of File, 1988-1999 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programming, 1987-1990 (Box 176, Folder 4-5, Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programming, 1991-2005 (Box 177, Folder 2-4)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programs - Private-Public Partnership/ProVenEx, 2000-2002 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programs - Global Philanthropy, 2000-2002 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programs - Global Philanthropy, 2000-2002 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2073
    - Program and Policy - Staff Volunteer Program, 2003-2004 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development, 1997-2005 (Box 181, Folder 3-4, Box 182, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development, 2006-2011 (Box 182, Folder 3-4, Box 183, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development, 2012-2013 (Box 178, Folder 5, Box 180, Folder 1-5, Box 181, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development, 2012-2013 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Supplementary Material (Box 183, Folder 3-4, Box 184, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Areas of Work, 2002-2004 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Convenings, 2011 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Convenings, 2011 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Core Competencies, 1998 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Operations Strategy Task Force, 2003-2005 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Program Strategy Task Force, 2005 (Box 185, Folder 2, Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Nanotechnology, 2003-2007 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Retreats and Meetings, 1998-2011 (Box 187, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Sustainable Livelihoods, 1998 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Values, 1998-2012 (Box 187, Folder 4)